royalenfield.com 2008-12-17

# Royal Enfield | Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**    
Welcome to the website of Royal Enfield, a unit of Eicher Motors Limited. Royal Enfield provides this Site as a service to its customers and prospective buyers. Please review our Privacy Policy.

  **What this Privacy Policy covers**  
This Privacy Policy covers Royal Enfield's treatment of personally identifiable information that Royal Enfield collects when you are on the site. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Royal Enfield does not own or control, or to people that Royal Enfield does not employ or manage.

  **Information Collection and Usage**  
Royal Enfield collects personally identifiable information when you register through the site and when you enter online promotions and contests. Royal Enfield may also receive personally identifiable information from business partners.

  When you register with Royal Enfield, we ask for your Name, Email address, Address, Zip Code, Birth date, Gender, Occupation, and bike ownership details. Once you register with Royal Enfield and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

  Royal Enfield also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested.

  Royal Enfield uses information for two general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain information, and to contact you about the latest info and new products.

  **Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
Royal Enfield will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.

  Royal Enfield will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:  
\- We have your consent to share the information;   
\- We need to share the information with business partners in order to respond to your comments or to resolve service related issues;  
\- We respond to requests from any Indian or foreign government, security, defence, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer;   
\- We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or   
\- We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Royal Enfield Terms of Service

  **Our use of "cookies"**  
As is the case with many sites, when you visit our site and complete a registration form, we will place a "cookie" on your computer, which helps us identify you more quickly when you return. We will not use "cookies" or other devices to follow your click stream on the Internet generally, but will use them, and other devices, to determine which pages or information you find most useful or interesting at our own Web sites.

  Most browsers permit you to refuse to accept a "cookie" offered by a Web site. You will not be denied access to any part of the website on account of your refusal to accept a "cookie," but your transactions through this Web site may be delayed due to the time it takes you to re-enter basic information necessary to complete a transaction.

  **Collection of information by third parties**  
Our Web pages may offer promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain Customer Identifiable Information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of this information and we encourage you to consult their privacy policies for more information on their privacy practices.

  **Security**  
Your Royal Enfield Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.

  **Links**  
To improve your Web experience, and to offer you products in which you might be interested, we provide links to business alliance companies, Royal Enfield dealers, and other third-party sites. When you click on these links, you will be transferred out of our Web site and connected to the Web site of the organization or company that you selected. Because Royal Enfield does not control these sites (even if an affiliation exists between our Web sites and a third party site), you are encouraged to review their individual privacy notices. If you visit a Web site that is linked to our sites, you should consult that site's privacy policy before providing any Customer Identifiable Information.

  **Changes to this privacy policy**  
Royal Enfield may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
